const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "what is the beautifull stadium in the world?",
        choices: ["Emirete stadium", "stanford bridge", "old traford", "anfield road"],
        correctAnswer: "Emirete stadium"
    },
    {
        question: "what is my favorite sport?",
        choices: ["Soccer", "Baseball", "Footbal", "Swimming"],
        correctAnswer: "Soccer"
    },
    {
        question: "what is your favorite place to visit?",
        choices: ["barcelona", "maldives", "Hewan Rock church", "samien maunt"],
        correctAnswer: "Hewan Rock church"
    },
    {
        question: "What is my favorite sports?",
        choices: ["Soccer", "Baseball", "Footbal", "Swimming"],
        correctAnswer: "Soccer"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the best TV show I like?",
        choices: ["Steve Harvey show", "little big shot", "ESPN sport soccer", "sunday suplement"],
        correctAnswer: "ESPN sport show"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the worst battle feild ever happened in human history?",
        choices: ["the battle of Adwa", "the battle of stalingrad", "the six day war", "yom kippur"],
        correctAnswer: "the battle of Stalingrad"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the best meal of the day ?",
        choices: ["breakfast", "lunch", "dinner", "snack"],
        correctAnswer: "breakfast"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the best book that I whould love to read?",
        choices: ["long walk to freedom", "maths book", "football magazine", "news paper"],
        correctAnswer: "Long walk to freedom"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the best thing to do on the sutarday?",
        choices: ["cooking", "cleaning", "sleeping", "playing sport"],
        correctAnswer: "cleaning"
    },
    {
        question: "what is the best movie of altime?",
        choices: ["God must be crazy", "kunta kunte", "the matrix", "law and order"],
        correctAnswer: "God must be crazy"
    }
 ];
 